- Remove trash and legacy
- Github
- Build Script
- Architektur dokumentieren

- DNF Normalization of boolean expression:
  The trait exists in intermediate-representation/lms/extensions/normalization.
  But, normalized queries need to be simplified again, otherwise they produce unwieldy large ASTs

- Ordering of boolean expressions (or the resulting atomar selection conditions):
  The ordering exists in intermediate-representation/lms/extensions/normalization.
  Ordering is important to simplifiy queries using the same conditions (i.e., a && b && a => a && b)
  But, ordered queries still produce unwieldy large ASTs

- Selections will be propagated as far as possible and thus some operators, steming from
  boolean normalizations can not be removed again.
  E.g., if x and y are conditions on the types of a and b respectively then:
  σ_{x || y}(a × b) 
  <=> 
  σ_{x}(a × b) ∪ σ_{y}(a × b) 
  <=> 
  (σ_{x}(a) × b) ∪ (a × σ_{y}(b))

- Ordering of existential conditions:
  Existentials should be processed last. The reason being that they create cross products with the preceeding queries.
  Thus the preceeding query should already be optimized and minimal.
  Otherwise trailing boolean conditions may produce large ASTs that can not be optimized again (or are very hard to optimize).
  This is connected to the fact that selections will be propagated as far as possible and thus some operators, steming from
  boolean normalizations can not be removed again.







